<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JiangLX Lab</title>
    <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JiangLX Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; JiangLX Lab, 2020 </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Li-Xi Jiang Lab</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! This is home page of Li-Xi Jiang lab, Zhejiang University.
Most information about our lab can be found here, if you find anything you are interested in, please feel free to contact us.
BTW, welcome graduate or undergraduate students to contact Professor Jiang:
 email: jianglx@zju.edu.cn Phone: 0571-88982905. Address: Building A Room 367.  Happy 2020!
taoyan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Courses Of JiangLX Lab</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/class/class/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 14:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/class/class/</guid>
      <description>Agriculture for Healthy Human Life description
 Agriculture for Healthy Human Life for undergraduate students, special course in summer semester for freshmen of Chu Kochen Honors College
 High Efficient Ese of Natural Resources in Crops description
 High Efficient Ese of Natural Resources in Crops for undergraduate students, special course in summer semester for freshmen of Chu Kochen Honors College
 Plant Molecular Physiology description
 Plant Molecular Physiology for undergraduate students, special course in summer semester for freshmen of Chu Kochen Honors College</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome-wide association study reveals new genes involved in leaf trichome formation in polyploid oilseed rape (Brassica napus L.)</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication01/</guid>
      <description>More please read this paper online or download it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release for website</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>We release our lab&#39;s website.
taoyan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whole-Genome Resequencing of a Worldwide Collection of Rapeseed Accessions Reveals the Genetic Basis of Ecotype Divergence</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication02/</guid>
      <description>More please read this paper online or download it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRANSPARENT TESTA 4‐mediated flavonoids negatively affect embryonic fatty acid biosynthesis in Arabidopsis</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication04/</guid>
      <description>More please read this paper online or download it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>De-Zhi Wu</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/member/wudezhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/member/wudezhi/</guid>
      <description>Publications   Kuang LH#, Shen QF#, Wu LY, Yu JH, Fu LB, Wu DZ*, Zhang GP. Identification of microRNAs responding to salt stress in barley by high-throughput sequencing and degradome analysis. Environ Exp Bot, 2019, Accepted.
  Wu DZ#, Liang Z#, Yan T, Xu Y, Xuan LJ, Tang J, Zhou G, Lohwasser U, Hua SJ, Wang HY, Chen XY, Wang Q, Zhu L, Maodzeka A, Hussain N, Li Z, Li X, Shamsi IH, Jilani G, Wu L, Zheng H, Zhang GP, Chalhoub B, Shen L, Yu H, Jiang LX*.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Li-Xi Jiang</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/member/jianglx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/member/jianglx/</guid>
      <description>Publications Selected Papers   Wu D, Liang Z, Yan T, Xu Y, Xuan L, Tang J, Zhou G, Lohwasser U, Hua S, Wang H, Wang Q, Zhu L, Maodzeka A, Hussain N, Li Z, Li X, Shamsi IH, Jilani G, Wu L, Zheng H, Zhang G, Chalhoub B, Shen L, Yu H, Jiang LX (2019). Whole-genome resequencing of a world-wide collection of rapeseed accessions reveals genetic basis of their ecotype divergence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effect of high night temperature on storage lipids and transcriptome changes in developing seeds of oilseed rape</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication03/</guid>
      <description>More please read this paper online or download it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effect of seed dormancy degree on oil content of rapeseed and the underlying molecular mechanisms</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/project/project1-seed_dormancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/project/project1-seed_dormancy/</guid>
      <description>There are various factors that affect seed oil formation. Our previous research discovered that the rapeseed oil content declines after reaching a peak point. In some years with heavy rainfall before harvest time, seeds of some rapeseed genotype germinate on maternal plant, which causes decrease of fatty acid levels in seeds and the damage of seed quality. In this study, we aim to investigate:
 the genotypic variation of seed dormancy degree; the association between premature-seed dormancy and fatty-acid level redcution at maturing stage of rapeseed; the differences of transcriptome between developing and germinating seeds, and the key regulators leading to the differences; the feasibilities to promote seed dormancy by manipulating relevant genes and/or selecting allelic variations favorable to premature-seed dormancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tao Yan</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/member/taoyan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/member/taoyan/</guid>
      <description>Tao Yan is a PhD student of Crop Genetics and Breeding at the Zhejiang University Crop Science Lab. My Ph.D research work covers a range of issues : Population Genetics Evolution and Ecotype Divergence Analysis of oilseed Rape, Genome-wide Association Study (GWAS) of Agronomic Traits. Currently, He is interested in Transposable Elements Insertion Polymorphisms (TIPs) in Crop Population and genetic basis such as SV, CNV and TIPs etc shapes the diversity of different morphotypes of B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional analysis and mutagenesis of GDSL genes for breeding oilseed rape (B. napus) with higher oil content</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/project/project3-gdsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/project/project3-gdsl/</guid>
      <description>To increase seed oil content, many efforts have been made on the promotion of lipid biosynthesis efficiency, but little attention has been paid on the blocking of lipid decomposition in the process of oil accumulation. SFARs are defined as GDSL-type lipase genes that are expressed in seeds. They hydrolyze triacylglycerol and reduce the accumulation of seed lipids. Preliminary studies unveiled that the disruption of 5 genes (SFAR1 - SFAR5) resulted in significant increases of fatty acids (FA) in seeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Molecular mechansim of oil-yield formation in oilseed rape (Brassica napus)</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/project/project2-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/project/project2-oil/</guid>
      <description>This is a Key Project for Basic Research (abbreviated as 973 Project), administrated by Ministry of Science and Technology in PR China. Goal of the research is to understand the molecular basis of oil-yield formation in oilseed rape (Brassica napus). There are six workpackages in this 973 project. We are responsible for the workpachage, namely, identification of inhibitors of lipid biosynthesis and the reducers of lipids in developing oilseeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRANSPARENT TESTA8 Inhibits Seed Fatty Acid Accumulation by Targeting Several Seed Development Regulators in Arabidopsis</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication06/</guid>
      <description>More please read this paper online or download it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRANSPARENT TESTA2 regulates embryonic fatty acid biosynthesis by targeting FUSCA3 during the early developmental stage of Arabidopsis seeds</title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/publication/publication05/</guid>
      <description>More please read this paper online or download it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/cloud/bnasnpdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/cloud/bnasnpdb/</guid>
      <description>BnaSNPDB: SNP Database of Brassica napus L.   Overview The SNP database of Brassica napus L. (BnaSNPDB) is an interactive web portal that provides multiple analysis modules to visualize and explore SNPs among 1007 rapeseed germplasm accessions based on the data reported by previous research (Wu et al., 2019). The app is deployed at http://121.41.229.126:3838/bnasnpdb and http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn:3838/bnasnpdb for online use. The whole dataset and code of BnaSNPDB is available at https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/cloud/gwas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/cloud/gwas/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Rapeseed (Brassica napus L.) is an important source of edible oil and protein-rich livestock feed in the world. B. napus (AACC) was ancestrally originated from an interspecific hybridization between two diploid progenitors, B. rapa (AA) (n = 10) and B. oleracea (CC) (n = 9), less than 7500 years ago. In our previous study, we resequenced a world-wide collection of 991 B. napus gerplasm accessions, including 658 winter types, 145 semi-winter types and 188 spring types, from 39 countries (Wu et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rapeseed.zju.edu.cn/research/</guid>
      <description>JiangLX Lab Li-Xi Jiang lab studies Molecular mechansim of oil-yield formation in oilseed rape (Brassica napus)、 the effect of seed dormancy degree on oil content of rapeseed and the underlying molecular mechanisms and the genomics of rapeseed genetic resources
Research Focus  Molecular mechanism of lipid formation in Brassica oilseeds; Genomics of rapeseed genetic resources; Prediction of heterosis on the basis of the resequencing data of parental lines.  Current research projects Molecular mechansim of oil-yield formation in oilseed rape (Brassica napus)   Project code: 2015CB250100</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>